vilvin.net 2014-02-19

# Vilvin.net - Privacy Policy

_Effective Date: May 01, 2013_

* * *

This privacy policy applies to https://www.vilvin.net/ owned and operated by Vilvin Technologies Inc. ("Vilvin", "We", "Us", "Our"). This privacy policy describes how Vilvin collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Vilvin Technologies Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site https://www.vilvin.net/ and does not cover information that may be collected through our Advertising Partners’ websites or by any other third party business affiliates.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@vilvin.net. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

## 1 INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE

**We may collect the following personal information from you in various contexts:**

1) Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number  
2) Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address  
3) Financial Information such as bank account numbers and payment escrow service PIN number  
4) Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password  
5) Demographic information such as age

**We use this information to:**

1) Personalize your experience - Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs  
2) Improve our website - We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you  
3) Improve customer service - Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs  
4) Process transactions  
5) Administer your account  
6) Send you a confirmation email and account status related communications

**ID Validation and Data Supplementation**  
We may ask for additional personal information if you wish to link your bank account with our transaction services in order to validate your identity. Acceptable forms of ID verification may include copies of your Driving License, Passport, Social Security Number or National ID, TAX ID or Public sector employees ID card. We may also request a bank statement, electricity, phone, gas, cable or internet bill. Any facsimiles of sensitive information are destroyed after verification is complete.

We may cross reference information about you from third party sources such as your preferred payment escrow service, to further validate your identity and prevent fraud.

## 2 INFORMATION SHARING

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Service Providers:** We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your transactions. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us and are obligated to keep your information confidential.

**Frames:** Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our site. Please be aware that you are interacting with and may be providing your personal information to these third parties and not to https://www.vilvin.net/

**Legal Disclaimer:** We may also disclose your personal information:

\- as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

\- when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

\- if Vilvin is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

\- to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

## 3 USER ACCESS AND CHOICE

If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, amend, remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at support@vilvin.net or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. If you no longer desire our service, you may deactivate/delete your account by contacting us directly. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 4 TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES/COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. However, we do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use these cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

**Web Beacons/Gifs:** Some of our third party advertising partners employ a software technology called clear gifs or pixels (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**Analytics/Log Files** : As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**3rd Party Tracking:** : The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets (such as social media) on the site is not covered by our privacy policy. These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site. We do not have access or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

**Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting:** We partner with a third party ad network to both display advertising on our Web site and to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests and track which ads you click on. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We use Adhitz Ads to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Adhitz’s Privacy page: <http://www.adhitz.com/en/Privacy_Policy>

## 5 SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. We encrypt the transmission of all information submitted through our site using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@vilvin.net

## 6 ADDITIONAL INFOMRATION

**Links to 3rd Party Sites:** Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Vilvin. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Forum:** Our Web site offers a publicly accessible community forum. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [email]. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Social Media Widgets:** Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as links to Facebook and Twitter. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Changes To This Policy:** We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## 7 CONTACT US

You may write to us or contact us using the details below regarding privacy issues:

 **Vilvin Software Solutions Private Limited**  
5/6 Second east cross street  
Tirunelveli, Tamilnadu 627001 India  
 **Phone:** +91 9597874464  
 **Email:** support@vilvin.net 

**Vilvin Technologies Inc**  
40 E. Main Street, No. 275  
Newark, Delaware 19711 U.S.A  
 **Phone:** +1 302 722 6273  
 **Email:** support@vilvin.net
